

Anna Clarissa Aranas

Web Developer

A skilled Web Developer with 4 years of relevant work experience in building, maintaining, and enhancing system websites. Love doing the logic and challenges of programming, solving creative problems, and giving quality work. Motivated to advance and expand my skill set through self-paced learning, targeted mentorship, and challenging projects.

Contact

Address

National Road, Panilao, Pilar, Bataan

Email

annaclarissaaranas09@gmail.com

Phone

- +639453771357
- +639761152473

Portfolio

https://acda0209.github.io

Expertise

- NodeJS, ExpressJS, AdonisJS
 TypeScript, NestJS, ReactJS
- PHP/Laravel
- C#/ASP MVC
- MySQL, SQL Server, MongoDB
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Jauery, Bootstrap
- VB.Net, VB6

Work Experience

Oct 2022 -2023

Full-Stack Web Developer | Freelance Project: Sequrr

- Develop a web app for Real Estate Agency management & compliance solution using Node.js and Express for creating back-end and APIs with MongoDB as a primary database, and PHP for the client-side.
- Additional tools used are: Twilio, OCR labs, Stripe and Google Maps

Sept 2021 -Oct 2022

Programmer Analyst II | Accenture Project: SE LH CN Java - ABI Aurora

Project: SE LH CN AWS – PEXA Capacity Services

- Creating microservices for system maintenance and enhancements
- API Integration using NestJS, Swagger UI
- Implementing Domain-Driven Design approach
- Unit Testing using Mocha, Chai, Sinon
- Data streaming and messaging services using Event Hub and Service Bus
- Log Management using DataDog
- Data persisting using MongoDB
- Git Repository and Running pipeline (Azure DevOps)
- Bugs fixing and issue resolution (SonarQube for code quality)
- Monitoring and creating dashboards and alerts for application logs
- Practicing Scrum and Implementing Agile Methodology

Feb 2019-Mar 2021

Web Developer | Holborn Assets Project: Adviser Connect, Leading Edge, Autodialer, Helpdesk

- Creating different web application using different frameworks
- CRM web application consisting of other Holborn's existing systems, such as Leading Edge, Fact Finder, Digital Marketing, Back Broker Office and etc..
 - Developed using ASP MVC and SQL Server
- Lead Affiliate and management system using NodeJS, AdonisJS and MySQL (first developed using Laravel)
- Helpdesk app using AdonisJS, Express, WebSocket and MySQL
- Practicing Scrum and Implementing Agile Methodology

Tools

VSCode, GIT, Bitbucket, Azure

DevOps, Jira, Confluence,

Postman, Photoshop, MS Office

Education

2013-2017 4 years

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Major in Net and Web Application
Bataan Peninsula State University